Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Contracts for Broadcasting, 1929-1949; undated; 1
  - Standard Brands--Royal Desserts and Fleischmann's Yeast--Rudy Vallee Program, 1938-1939; 74
    - F. Chase Taylor (Stoopnagle), 1938 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Farewell--Consent, 1939 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Fay Wray, 1939 June 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ferdinand the Bull--Consent, 1938 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Five Minutes--Consent, 1938 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - For Value Received--Consent, 1938 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frances Langford, 1938 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Francis Lederer, 1939 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Frank Craven, 1938 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Franklin P. Adams, 1938 Aug. 11; Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Franklin P. Adams, 1939 June 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Freddie Bartholomew--Consent, 1938 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gabby Hartnett, 1939 Mar. 16; Aug. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - Gaby Hartnett, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gale Page, 1939 Apr. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - George Givot, 1938 Oct. 13; Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gertrude Lawrence, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gertrude Lawrence, 1939 Sept. 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ginger Manners, 1939 Apr. 20; May11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Gladys George, 1938 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Grace Moore, 1939 June 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Graham McNamee, 1939 Feb. 2-Mar. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Guy Kibbee, 1939 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 147)
    - Hal LeRoy, Ruth Dodd, 1938 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - Harold Vermilyea, 1938 July 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - Helen Claire, 1938 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Helen Kane, 1939 July 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1939 May 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Herbert Mundin, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Hiram Sherman, 1938 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - Home Town--Consent, 1939 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Hugh Herbert, 1938 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Hugh Herbert, 1939 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Hugh Herbert, Anita Pam, 1938 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - I Do--Consent, 1938 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - In the Fold--Consent, 1939 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ina Claire, 1938 July 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - Interview at the Ballet--Consent, 1938 July 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Irvin S. Cobb, 1939 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jack Oakie, 1939 Mar. 23; Apr. 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jack Pearl, 1939 July 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - James Hilton, 1939 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jane Warren, 1938 Nov. 24; Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Jane Warren, 1938 Dec. 8-1939 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jenny Learns Quickly--Consent, 1939 July 27 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jerome "Dizzy" Dean, 1939 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jerry Colona, 1939 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jerry Lester, 1939 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jessie Royce Landis, 1938 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1938 July 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1939 Feb. 23-Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jimmy McCallion, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Joan Tetzel, 1939 May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Joe Cook, 1938 Sept. 8; Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Joe Cook, 1939 Mar. 2; Aug. 10 (Film-reel 147)
    - Joe DiMaggio, 1938 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Joe E. Louis, 1938 Aug. 4; 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Joe Sodja, 1938 July 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Joe the Motorman--Consent, 1939 June 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Joey Faye, 1939 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - John Barrymore, 1939 Aug. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - John Buckmaster, 1939 Mar. 9; May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - John Phillip Marquand, 1939 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - John Pugliese, 1938 Aug. 18; 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - John Williams, 1939 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Jose Ferrer, 1938 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1938 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Judith Anderson, 1939 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Judy, Annie and Zeke Canova, 1938 July 7; Sept. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - June Sillman, 1939 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Kathleen Morris, 1939 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Kay Francis, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ken Darby and quartet, 1938 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ken Murray, 1938 Sept. 22; Nov. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Knickerbocker Holiday--Consent, 1938 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lady Chamberlain's Pearls--Consent, 1938 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Laurence Olivier, 1939 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Laurette Taylor, 1939 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1939 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Leon Belasco, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Leon Janney, 1939 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lillian Settanni, 1938 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lindsay MacHarris, 1938 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lionel Barrymore, 1938 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lou Holtz, 1938 July 7; Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lou Holtz, 1939 May 25-Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lou Parker, Teddy Hart and the services of one girl, 1938 Sept. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lupe Velez, 1938 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lynn Farnol, 1938 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - Lynn Murray, 1939 June 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lynn Murray and 12 voices, 1939 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Lynn Murray and chorus, 1939 Aug. 10-31 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mamba's Daughters--Consent, 1939 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marek Windheim, 1939 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Margo, 1939 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marie Wilson, 1939 Jan. 12; Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Marjorie Main, 1938 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Martha Scott, 1939 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mary Joy, Elaine Aley, 1939 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mary Martin, 1939 Feb. 2; 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Bert Lahr--Consent, 1939 Mar. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Cliff Arquette, 1938 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Dave Oliver--Consent, 1939 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Jack Oakie--Consent, 1939 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Jerry Lester--Consent, 1939 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 147)
    - Material for Royal-Fleischmann--Consent, 1939 Apr. 6-May 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Maurice de Abranavel, 1938 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Maurice Evans, 1938 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Maurice Evans, 1939 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - Max Baer, 1939 May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Max Schuster, 1938 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Maxie Rosenbloom, 1938 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - May Robson, 1939 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - McKay Morris, 1939 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Meet the Folks--Consent, 1938 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Michael Brooks, 1939 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Milton and Marshall, 1939 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Miriam Hopkins, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mischa Levitzki, 1938 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Miss Pringle Gets a Ticket--Consent, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Missouri Legend--Consent, 1938 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - Mona Morgan, 1938 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - More of the Life of Henry Aldrich--Consent, 1938 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Morton Thompson, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Mr. Pip--Consent, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Mrs. Jean Drilling, 1939 June 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. Richardson and quartet, 1939 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 147)
    - Mrs. Weems and the Wanderlust--Consent, 1938 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Muriel Hutchinson, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Nana Bryant, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - No More Battles--Consent, 1938 May 18 (Film-reel 147)
    - Norman Rockwell, 1938 July 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ogden Nash, 1939 July 14 (Film-reel 147)
    - Olsen and Johnson, 1938 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - Olsen and Johnson, 1939 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 147)
    - Onslow Stevens, 1938 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Open Window--Consent, 1939 May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Oswald and (Ernie) Stanton, 1938 Sept. 15; Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Owen Davis Jr., 1939 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paloma Ephron, 1939 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Pat C. Flick, Eddie Conrad, 1939 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Gerritts, 1938 Oct. 20; Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Paul Gerritts, 1938 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Paul Lukas, 1938 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Paul Robeson, 1939 June 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Pep Talk--Consent, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Peter Lorre, 1939 Aug. 10 (Film-reel 147)
    - Prof. Gossamer's Experiment--Consent, 1938 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Rae Samuels, 1938 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Rags Ragland, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Raymond Massey, 1938 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - Reginald Ellis, 1939 May 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Resurrection--Consent, 1939 Feb. 9; Apr. 6 (Film-reel 147)
    - Richard Bartholomess, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Richard Haydn, 1939 Feb. 2-Mar. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Robert Morley, 1939 Mar. 9; May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Robert W. Ballin, Reynold T. McEvoy, 1938 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - Roses for Miss Fifi--Consent, 1939 Aug. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - Russell Birdwell, 1939 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 147)
    - Ruth (Glascott) Fair, 1938 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ruth Hilde Somer, 1938 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Sally Eilers, 1939 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sam Levene, 1939 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sanctuary--Consent, 1939 May 11 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sea Fever--Consent, 1938 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Shadow Play--Consent, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Sheila Barrett, 1938 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Sheila Barrett, 1939 Mar. 9; Aug. 3 (Film-reel 147)
    - Shirley Booth, 1939 July 27; Sept. 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Simon Barer, 1939 May 25 (Film-reel 147)
    - Slim and Slam, 1938 July 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Somerset Maugham, 1939 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Stanley Jones, Miller and Manten, 1938 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Stanley Jones, Miller and Manten, 1938 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - Sterling Holloway, 1938 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Still Alarm--Consent, 1939 July 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Stroud Twins, 1938 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Stroud Twins, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - Suppressed Desires--Consent, 1939 July 7 (Film-reel 147)
    - Surprise for the Boys--Consent, 1939 Aug. 10 (Film-reel 147)
    - Swan Song--Consent, 1939 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Tartar Sauce--Consent, 1938 July 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ted Lewis, 1938 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Test Flight--Consent, 1938 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Batchelors, 1938 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Bayou--Consent, 1939 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Belmont Balladiers, 1938 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Breaking Point--Consent, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Cavaliers, 1938 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Early Life of Henry Aldrich--Consent, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Four Squires, 1938 Nov. 24; Dec. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Foursome, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Gift--Consent, 1939 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Highwayman--Consent, 1939 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Light--Consent, 1938 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Little Dove--Consent, 1938 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Man in Possession--Consent, 1939 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Oxford Boys, 1938 July 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Primary Facts--Consent, 1939 June 29 (Film-reel 147)
    - The Quintones, 1938 July 14; 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - The Rock--Consent, 1938 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 147)
    - There's Always Joe Winters--Consent, 1939 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 147)
    - Thomas Mitchell, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Tito and His Swingtette, 1938 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Tom Howard, George Shelton, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Tony Labriola, Ernie Stanton, 1939 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 147)
    - Travelogue--Consent, 1939 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 147)
    - Trilby--Consent, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Under the Skin, 1939 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 147)
    - Use of name "Dagenham Girl Pipers Band"--Consent, 1939 June 22 (Film-reel 147)
    - Vincent Lopez, 1938 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Wallace (Wally) Brown, 1938 Sept. 29-Oct. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Wallace Brown, 1938 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Walter Connolly, 1938 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Walter Hampden, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Walter Huston, 1938 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Walter Huston, 1939 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1938 Sept. 1; Oct. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1939 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 147)
    - Walter Slezak, 1938 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Wealth and Wisdom--Consent, 1939 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 147)
    - Wedding Present--Consent, 1939 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - Who Is at the Dike--Consent, 1938 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - William A. Brady, Grace George, 1938 Sept. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - William Frawley, 1939 Jan. 12; Mar. 16 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Gargan, 1939 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Post Jr., 1939 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Spargrove, 1939 May 25-Sept. 21 (Film-reel 147)
    - William Wilson--Consent, 1938 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - William Wilson--Consent, 1939 May 4 (Film-reel 147)
    - Willie Howard, 1938 July 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Willie Howard, 1939 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 147)
    - Wishful Thinking--Consent, 1939 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 147)
    - Wynn Murray, 1939 June 1 (Film-reel 147)
    - Zane Grey, 1938 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 147)
    - Zazu Pitts, 1938 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 146)
  - Standard Brands--Royal Gelatin--Rudy Vallee Program, 1931-1939; 75
    - A.L. Alexander, 1937 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Abie's Irish Rose--Consent, 1937 May 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - Adelaide Klein, 1936 Nov. 19; 1937 July 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Al Golden, 1938 June 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Albert Sullivan, 1937 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Aldous Huxley, 1937 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - All Points West--Consent, 1937 Jan. 7; Feb. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Andy Kerr, 1936 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ann Deere, 1936 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ann Rutledge, 1938 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ann Seymour, 1937 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Anna May Wong, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Another Language--Consent, 1934 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Anrea Leeds, 1938 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Arlene Jackson, 1936 July 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Arnold Korff, 1937 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Arthur Allen, 1938 May 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Arthur Byron, 1938 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Autumn Flower--Consent, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Averill Harris, 1937 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Babes in Arms--Consent, 1937 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Barney Brant, 1939 (Film-reel 146)
    - Baron Giorgio Suriani, 1937 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - Battle for D'Artagnan--Consent, 1938 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Beatrice Fairfax, 1938 May 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - Beatrice Howell, 1937 June 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1932-1937 (Film-reel 146)
    - Begin at the End--Consent, 1938 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ben Grauer, 1938 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Benny Krueger and Orchestra, 1932 (Film-reel 146)
    - Benny Ryan, Harriet Lee, 1937 Mar. 25; Apr. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bernard Bierman, 1937 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bert Lahr, 1933; 1937 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bert Wheeler, 1936 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Betsy Ayers, 1933 (Film-reel 146)
    - Betty Hanna, 1937 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Betty Philson, 1936 Dec. 24; 1937 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Beulah Bondi, 1938 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bill Robinson, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 146)
    - Billy Halop, 1936 Nov. 19; 1937 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bob Burns, 1937 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bob Hope, 1937 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bob Hope, Honey Chile, 1936 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bombo the Clown--Consent, 1937 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Boris Karloff, 1937 Nov. 11; 1938 May 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Bradford Kirkbride, 1936 Oct. 22; 1937 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Brian Aherne, 1937 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Burgess Meredith, 1937 Feb. 11; 1937 June 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Burgess Meredith, Margaret Perry, 1937 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cab Calloway and his pianist, 1936 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cappy Barra and His Harmonica Ensemble, 1937 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Captain Edward V. Rickenbacker, 1936 Aug. 21; 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Captain John H. Ayres, 1936 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Carl Kress, Dick McDonough, 1936 Aug. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Carlos Salzedo, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Carmel Meyers, 1938 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Casper Readon, 1936 July 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cast of St. Helena, 1936 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cat with the Golden Eyes--Consent, 1938 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cecelia Ager, 1937 July 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cedric Hardwicke, 1937 Apr. 22; 1938 June 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Charles De Zemler, 1937 June 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Charles Irwin, 1937 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Charles Ruggles, 1936 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Charlie Withers, 1936 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - Chic Kennedy, 1938 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Church Mouse--Consent, 1934 Nov. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Claude Dempier, Billy Carlisle, 1938 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Claude Rains, 1937 Apr. 29; July 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Clyde Fillmore, 1936 Dec. 31; 1937 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Colgate Glee Club, 1938 May 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Confession--Consent, 1937 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Conjure Drum--Consent, 1937 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Connie Goes Home--Consent, 1935 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Conrad Nagel, 1937 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 146)
    - Conway Tearle, 1937 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cookie Bowers, 1937 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Coquette--Consent, 1934 Sept. 18-Dec. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Corinne Griffith, 1937 July 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1936 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Cross and Dunn, 1937 June 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Curtain--Consent, 1937 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Daddy Long Legs--Consent, 1935 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dance Macabre--Consent, 1938 May 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dave Rubinoff, 1937 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 146)
    - Decision--Consent, 1937 June 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Deems Taylor, 1936 June 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dennis King, 1937 June 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Doc Rockwell, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 146)
    - Don Johnson, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Don Tannen, 1936 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Donald Cameron, 1937 Feb. 18; Apr. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Doris Hare, 1936 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Doris Nolan, 1937 Aug. 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dorothy Thompson, 1937 June 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Douglas Fairbanks Jr., 1937 July 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Douglas Leigh, 1937 July 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Douglas Montgomery, 1936 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Douglas Scott, 1937 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dr. Wolfgang Von Haden, 1936 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dropped Stitches--Consent, 1938 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 146)
    - Dudley Diggs, 1937 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 146)
    - East and Dumke, 1938 May 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Conrad and Company, 1936 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Garr, 1937 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Green, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Green, Dick Campbell, 1937 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Kay, 1936 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Peabody, 1936 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eddie Peabody, 1937 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 146)
    - Edith Barrett, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 146)
    - Edith Lorrand, 1936 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 146)
    - Edith Spencer, 1937 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Edward Arnold, 1937 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Effie Atherton, 1938 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elaine Barrie, 1937 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eleanor Tenant, 1937 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eliseo Grenet and Orchestra, 1936 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elizabeth Day, 1936 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elizabeth Patterson, 1937 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elsa Maxwell, 1936 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elsa Rahr, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elsie Houston, 1938 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 146)
    - Elsworth Vines, 1937 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eric Blore, 1937 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eric Linden, 1938 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Erik Rolf, 1937 Apr. 8; 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Erin O'Brien (Moore), 1936-1937 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ethel Barrymore, 1937 Dec. 23; 1938 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ethel Blume, 1937 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ethel Merman, 1937 May 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eustace Wyatt, 1936 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Eva Jessye Choir, 1937 Aug. 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - Ever After--Consent, 1938 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 146)
    - F. Chase Taylor (Stoopnagle), 1938 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fan Burke, 1936 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fanny Brice, 1933; 1937 June 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fay Bainter, 1938 Feb. 3; Mar. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fay Wray, 1937 July 15; 1938 Feb. 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fedinand the Bull--Consent, 1938 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Florence Desmond, 1937 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 146)
    - Florence Reed, 1937 May 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Florida Friebus, 1937 Apr. 8; June 17 (Film-reel 146)
    - Folios, 1933 Dec.-1936 May (Film-reel 146)
    - For Future Reference--Consent, 1938 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Forever After--Consent, 1935 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frances Faye, 1936 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frances Fuller, 1937 Jan. 21; Aug. 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - Francis Lederer, 1936 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Buck, 1936 July 10 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Capra, 1937 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Case, 1937 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Conroy, 1938 May 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Craven, 1937 Dec. 30; 1938 June 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Fay, 1936 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Fay's Orchestra, 1936 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 146)
      Sam Middleton, Ben Creitz, Edward Spiwanck, Larry Wright, Marcia X. Johnstone, Ralph Lane, William K. Sabransky
    - Frank Gaby and Stooge, 1937 Feb. 11; 18 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Luther, Men About Town, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Sullivan, 1937 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frank Wilson, 1937 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - Frankie Thomas, 1937 June 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Franklin P. Adams, 1938 June 9; 23 (Film-reel 146)
    - Franz Bendsten, 1936 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Alvord, 1936 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Ardath, 1937 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Fisher and Band, 1938 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Hildebrand, 1937 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Keating, 1938 Apr. 21; June 2 (Film-reel 146)
    - Fred Perry, 1937 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gage Clark, 1936 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gene Autry, 1937 July 22; Oct. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gene Lockhart, 1937 Aug. 19 (Film-reel 146)
    - George Barnes, 1938 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 146)
    - George Goldsmith, 1938 May 12 (Film-reel 146)
    - George Olsen and Orchestra, 1933 (Film-reel 146)
    - Georgie Price, 1932 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gerald Hendricks, 1937 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gertrude Lawrence, 1936 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gertrude Nelson, 1938 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 146)
    - Girl of the Golden West--Consent, 1934 Nov. 1 (Film-reel 146)
    - Glenda Farrell, 1938 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 146)
    - Golden Boy--Consent, 1937 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 146)
    - Graham McNamee, 1935-1938 (Film-reel 146)
    - Grampa--Consent, 1938 May 26 (Film-reel 146)
    - Grant Gardner, 1937 Aug. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Grasiella Parrige, 1938 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gregory Ratoff, 1938 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 146)
    - Grover Jones, 1937 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gus Van, 1938 June 23 (Film-reel 146)
    - Gypsy Rose Lee, 1936 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 146)
    - H. Warden (Hack) Wilson, 1931-1933 (Film-reel 146)
    - Hamilton College Choir, 1937 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 146)
    - Hamlet--Consent, 1937 Aug. 5 (Film-reel 146)